♪Just wanna say hello♪
♪ فقط أريد أن أقول مرحبًا ♪
♪Hello♪
♪ مرحبا ♪
♪You are so unstoppable♪
♪ أنت لا يمكن إيقافك ♪
=Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2= =Episode 17=
= Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2 = = الحلقة 17 =
Miss Yun still hasn't come?
ملكة جمال يون ما زالت لم تأت؟
Never mind her.
لا تهتم لها.
I found it out.
لقد اكتشفت ذلك.
Miss Yun's mother had a new therapeutic scheme
والدة الآنسة يون لديها خطة علاجية جديدة
waiting for her to settle yesterday.
في انتظار أن تستقر أمس.
That's why she went back in a hurry.
لهذا السبب عادت على عجل.
So, everything about her mother
لذلك ، كل شيء عن والدتها
is settled now?
استقر الآن؟
Chu He.
تشو هي.
Do you think
هل تعتقد
I've been too strict
لقد كنت صارمًا جدًا
on Xiangxiang today?
في Xiangxiang اليوم؟
No.
رقم.
You made great sacrifice today too,
لقد قدمت تضحيات كبيرة اليوم أيضًا ،
boss.
رئيس.
You are not reminiscing, are you?
أنت لا تتذكر ، أليس كذلك؟
Chu He!
تشو هي!
How could you?
كيف استطعت؟
Ah.
آه.
Why am I thinking about that?
لماذا أفكر في ذلك؟
Call me Han.
اتصل بي هان.
Han.
هو.
Ay.
أوه.
Don't think about him anymore!
لا تفكر فيه بعد الآن!
You are so cute.
أنت جميل جدا.
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
What's your name?
ما اسمك؟
Do you like it?
هل أحببت ذلك؟
Yeah.
نعم.
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
I adopted this cat.
لقد اعتمدت هذه القطة.
Its name is Nuannuan.
اسمها Nuannuan.
Just like in your comic.
تماما كما هو الحال في فكاهي الخاص بك.
I don't know how to keep a cat.
لا أعرف كيف أحافظ على قطة.
You should be better at it.
يجب أن تكون أفضل في ذلك.
Can you take care of it for me?
هل يمكنك الاعتناء بها من أجلي؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
I really like kittens.
أنا حقا أحب القطط.
No.
رقم.
You are being weird today.
أنت غريب اليوم.
Why are you being so nice to me today?
لماذا أنت لطيف جدا معي اليوم؟
I went too far
ذهبت بعيدا جدا
yesterday.
في الامس.
I apologize.
أنا أعتذر.
No.
رقم.
It's fine.
لا بأس.
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
it's not entirely your fault.
ليس خطأك بالكامل.
Well.
نحن سوف.
Now you have Nuannuan.
الآن لديك Nuannuan.
You will take good care of it,
سوف تعتني به جيدًا ،
right?
الصحيح؟
Yeah.
نعم.
I definitely will.
أنا بالتأكيد سوف.
Is that right? Nuannuan?
هل هذا صحيح؟  Nuannuan؟
Well.
نحن سوف.
Will you take care of me
سوف يعتني بي
like you do to it?
كما تفعل به؟
Yeah.
نعم.
Wow.
رائع.
Boss.
رئيس.
I underestimated you.
لقد قللت من تقديرك.
You know quite well about flirting.
أنت تعلم جيدًا عن المغازلة.
You are so cute.
أنت جميل جدا.
Are you taking pictures of me?
هل تلتقط صورا لي؟
Not you, the cat.
ليس أنت القطة.
Give it to me.
اعطني اياه.
No.
رقم.
Let me have a look.
دعني ألقي نظرة.
Give it to me.
اعطني اياه.
Let me look!
دعني أنظر!
Boss.
رئيس.
How are the pictures?
كيف هي الصور؟
When are we going to buy presents for the Chairman?
متى سنشتري هدايا لرئيس مجلس الإدارة؟
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Okay.
تمام.